Okay, the next process you have is to decide if you need gray coverage, if you actually have gray hair showing and you need to cover gray.
That's the major reason why people want to color their hair.
You have to do your homework again on this because all colors are not created equal.
You're looking for 100% gray coverage on the box that you purchase.
So, it says on here, 100% gray coverage.
That's the process you're looking for.
This is a great root touch-up product because that's exactly what it's for, to touch up the roots and touch up the gray.
Make sure you read your instructions because it's going to tell you in the instructions.
Read them fully before you get started.
It's going to tell you how long to process based on how gray your hair is.
Some people have less gray than others.
Have you colored your hair previously or not.
Again, this is another product.
It says 100% long-lasting gray coverage, protects even fragile hair.
So if you have fine hair, make sure you're buying something for fragile fine hair.
If you don't have gray, I mean if you have gray here, you probably don't want to use a semi-permanent color because it's not going to cover your gray hair.
It's going to wash out and just give you some strange orange and pink highlights.
So when covering gray, make sure you're looking for something that has 100% gray coverage on the box and in the instructions.